1	Retweeted	retweeted	VBD	pos2=VBN	0	root	_	O
2	The	the	DT	_	3	det	_	B-ORG
3	Independent	independent	NNP	pos2=JJ	7	nmod	_	I-ORG
4	(	(	-LRB-	_	5	punct	_	I-ORG
5	@Independent	@independent	NNP	pos2=ADD	7	nmod	_	I-ORG
6	)	)	-RRB-	_	7	punct	_	I-ORG
7	:China	:china	NNP	pos2=NN	9	nsubj	_	L-ORG
8	is	be	VBZ	_	9	aux	_	O
9	censoring	censor	VBG	_	1	ccomp	_	O
10	people	people	NNS	_	9	dobj	_	O
11	calling	call	VBG	_	10	acl	_	O
12	North	north	NNP	_	13	compound	_	B-GPE
13	Korea	korea	NNP	_	15	poss	_	I-GPE
14	's	's	POS	_	13	case	_	L-GPE
15	leader	leader	NN	_	18	poss	_	O
16	'	'	POS	pos2=''	15	case	_	O
17	Kim	kim	NNP	_	18	compound	_	B-PERSON
18	Fatty	fatty	NNP	_	11	dobj	_	L-PERSON
19	the	the	DT	_	15	advmod	_	O
20	...	..	.	pos2=,	1	punct	_	O

1	https://t.co/XSE6zFx0kl	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	U-ORG

