1	Microsoft	microsoft	NNP	_	2	nsubj	_	U-ORG
2	joins	join	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
3	The	the	DT	pos2=NNP	5	det	_	B-ORG
4	Linux	linux	NNP	_	5	compound	_	I-ORG
5	Foundation	foundation	NNP	_	2	dobj	_	L-ORG
6	as	as	IN	_	2	prep	_	O
7	a	a	DT	_	9	det	_	O
8	Platinum	platinum	NNP	pos2=NN	9	compound	_	U-ORG
9	member	member	NN	_	6	pobj	_	O
10	|	|	SYM	pos2=,	18	punct	_	O
11	VentureBeat	venturebeat	NNP	_	18	dep	_	B-ORG
12	|	|	SYM	pos2=NFP	18	punct	_	I-ORG
13	Dev	dev	NNP	_	18	dep	_	L-ORG
14	|	|	SYM	pos2=NFP	18	punct	_	O
15	by	by	IN	_	13	prep	_	O
16	Emil	emil	NNP	_	17	compound	_	B-PERSON
17	Protalinski	protalinski	NNP	_	15	pobj	_	L-PERSON
18	https://t.co/aYNtERNqrQ	#hlink#	ADD	_	2	dep	_	O

