1	BREAKING	break	VBG	pos2=NN	6	nmod	_	O
2	-	-	:	pos2=HYPH	6	punct	_	O
3	Top	top	NNP	pos2=JJ	6	compound	_	O
4	Fox	fox	NNP	_	6	compound	_	B-ORG
5	News	news	NNP	_	6	compound	_	I-ORG
6	Host	host	NNP	pos2=NN	21	dep	_	L-ORG
7	to	to	IN	pos2=TO	8	aux	_	O
8	QUIT	quit	VB	pos2=NN	5	advcl	_	O
9	-	-	HYPH	pos2=:	8	punct	_	O
10	to	to	IN	pos2=TO	8	prep	_	O
11	Work	work	VB	pos2=NNP	10	pobj	_	O
12	for	for	IN	_	8	prep	_	O
13	Donald	donald	NNP	_	19	compound	_	B-PERSON
14	J.	j.	NNP	_	19	compound	_	I-PERSON
15	Trump	trump	NNP	_	19	compound	_	L-PERSON
16	#TrumpTransitionTeam	#trumptransitionteam	NNP	pos2=POS	19	compound	_	O
17	#Fox	#fox	NNP	_	19	compound	_	B-ORG
18	News	news	NNP	_	19	compound	_	L-ORG
19	#POTUS	#potus	NNP	pos2=POS	12	pobj	_	O
20	@SEC_SAM	@sec_sam	ADD	pos2=GW	21	dep	_	O
21	https://t.co/JiFxi5RsFl	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	O

