1	The	the	DT	_	3	det	_	O
2	latest	late	JJS	_	3	nmod	_	O
3	map	map	NN	_	7	nsubj	_	O
4	of	of	IN	_	3	prep	_	O
5	Western	western	NNP	pos2=JJ	6	compound	_	B-ORG
6	Mosul	mosul	NNP	_	4	pobj	_	L-ORG
7	shows	show	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
8	the	the	DT	_	9	det	_	O
9	control	control	NN	_	7	dobj	_	O
10	of	of	IN	_	9	prep	_	O
11	the	the	DT	_	13	det	_	O
12	main	main	JJ	_	13	nmod	_	O
13	road	road	NN	_	10	pobj	_	O
14	between	between	IN	_	13	prep	_	O
15	Mosul	mosul	NNP	_	17	compound	_	O
16	-	-	HYPH	_	17	punct	_	O
17	Raqqa	raqqa	NNP	_	14	pobj	_	O
18	by	by	IN	_	13	prep	_	O
19	Shia	shia	NNP	_	23	compound	_	B-PERSON
20	Hashid	hashid	NNP	_	23	compound	_	I-PERSON
21	al	al	NNP	_	23	compound	_	I-PERSON
22	-	-	HYPH	_	23	punct	_	I-PERSON
23	Shaabi	shaabi	NNP	_	24	compound	_	L-PERSON
24	mil	mil	NN	pos2=GW	18	pobj	_	O
25	…	…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	26	punct	_	O
26	https://t.co/qNTANnDn1E	#hlink#	ADD	_	24	appos	_	O

