1	#ZaynMalik	#zaynmalik	NNP	pos2=NNS	2	nsubj	_	O
2	GOT	get	VBD	pos2=VBN	0	root	_	O
3	TA	ta	NNP	pos2=NN	4	compound	_	B-GPE
4	ZAYN	zayn	NNP	_	5	compound	_	L-GPE
5	T-SHIRT	t-shirt	NN	pos2=NNP	7	compound	_	O
6	ZAYN	zayn	NNP	pos2=FW	7	compound	_	B-PERSON
7	MALIK	malik	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	L-PERSON
8	UNISEX	unisex	NN	pos2=JJ	9	compound	_	O
9	SHIRT	shirt	NN	pos2=NNP	10	compound	_	O
10	QUOTE	quote	NN	pos2=FW	15	compound	_	O
11	TUMBLR	tumblr	NNP	pos2=NN	13	compound	_	B-ORG
12	T	t	NNP	pos2=NN	13	compound	_	I-ORG
13	SHIRTS	shirt	NNPS	pos2=GW	18	compound	_	I-ORG
14	TEE	tee	NNP	pos2=NN	15	compound	_	I-ORG
15	PILLOWTALK	pillowtalk	NNP	pos2=-LRB-	16	dep	_	L-ORG
16	https://t.co/OWMjpInNUJ	#hlink#	ADD	_	18	dep	_	O
17	#OneDirection	#onedirection	ADD	pos2=-RRB-	0	root	_	O
18	#Zayne	#zayne	NNP	pos2=ADD	17	pobj	_	O

