1	NFL	nfl	NNP	_	4	compound	_	B-ORG
2	Latest	late	JJS	pos2=NNP	4	nmod	_	I-ORG
3	Trade	trade	NNP	pos2=NN	4	compound	_	I-ORG
4	Rumors	rumor	NNPS	pos2=NNS	0	root	_	I-ORG
5	&	&	CC	_	4	cc	_	I-ORG
6	Update	update	NN	pos2=VB	4	conj	_	L-ORG
7	:	:	:	_	4	punct	_	O
8	Trevor	trevor	NNP	_	10	compound	_	B-PERSON
9	Siemian	siemian	NNP	_	10	compound	_	L-PERSON
10	Unfazed	unfazed	NNP	pos2=JJ	4	acl	_	O
11	With	with	IN	_	10	prep	_	O
12	Potential	potential	NNP	_	11	pobj	_	O
13	Coming	come	VBG	pos2=NNP	4	acl	_	O
14	Of	of	IN	pos2=RB	13	prep	_	O
15	Tony	tony	NNP	_	16	compound	_	B-PERSON
16	Romo	romo	NNP	_	14	pobj	_	L-PERSON
17	To	to	IN	pos2=NNP	13	prep	_	O
18	Denver	denver	NNP	_	17	pobj	_	U-GPE
19	…	…	NFP	pos2=NNP	4	discourse	_	O
20	https://t.co/ss9eZQKiFV	#hlink#	ADD	_	4	appos	_	U-GPE

