1	BOOK	book	NN	pos2=VB	2	compound	_	O
2	PREVIEW	preview	NN	pos2=VB	4	compound	_	O
3	#Sovereignty	#sovereignty	NNP	pos2=NN	4	compound	_	B-ORG
4	Conflicts	conflict	NNS	pos2=NNPS	0	root	_	I-ORG
5	&	&	CC	pos2=GW	4	cc	_	I-ORG
6	Solution	solution	NN	pos2=NNP	4	conj	_	L-ORG
7	https://t.co/vttLlQEFjE	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=VBP	3	appos	_	O
8	#Rawls	#rawls	NNS	pos2=VBZ	11	compound	_	O
9	#Jurisprudence	#jurisprudence	NN	pos2=IN	10	compound	_	O
10	#Malvinas	#malvinas	NNS	pos2=NNPS	11	compound	_	O
11	#Falklands	#falklands	NNS	pos2=POS	7	ccomp	_	B-PERSON
12	#Gibraltar	#gibraltar	NNP	pos2=VBP	13	compound	_	I-PERSON
13	#Jerusalem	#jerusalem	NNP	pos2=PRP	11	appos	_	L-PERSON

