1	@OmegaMan34	@omegaman0	NN	pos2=NNS	5	nsubj	_	O
2	@csquared45	@csquared0	IN	pos2=NN	1	prep	_	O
3	North	north	NNP	_	4	compound	_	B-GPE
4	Korea	korea	NNP	_	5	nsubj	_	L-GPE
5	releases	release	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
6	video	video	NN	pos2=IN	5	dobj	_	O
7	of	of	IN	_	6	prep	_	O
8	Kim	kim	NNP	_	11	compound	_	B-PERSON
9	Jong	jong	NNP	_	11	compound	_	I-PERSON
10	-	-	HYPH	_	11	punct	_	I-PERSON
11	un	un	NNP	pos2=NN	7	pobj	_	L-PERSON
12	firing	fire	VBG	pos2=NN	5	advcl	_	O
13	a	a	DT	_	14	det	_	O
14	handgun	handgun	NN	_	12	dobj	_	O
15	The	the	DT	pos2=NNP	16	det	_	B-ORG
16	Telegraph	telegraph	NNP	pos2=NN	11	appos	_	I-ORG
17	https://t.co/bChhDIfsru	#hlink#	ADD	_	16	appos	_	L-ORG

