1	#Spurs	#spurs	NNS	pos2=NNP	2	compound	_	O
2	#GoSpursGo	#gospursgo	NNP	pos2=RB	0	root	_	O
3	1997	0	CD	_	5	qmod	_	B-DATE
4	-	-	SYM	pos2=HYPH	5	punct	_	I-DATE
5	98	0	CD	_	6	nmod	_	L-DATE
6	#Topps	#topps	NNS	pos2=CD	7	compound	_	O
7	ROOKIE	rookie	NN	_	2	appos	_	O
8	of	of	IN	_	7	prep	_	O
9	TIM	tim	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	B-PERSON
10	DUNCAN	duncan	NNP	pos2=NN	11	compound	_	L-PERSON
11	#	#	NN	_	8	pobj	_	O
12	115	0	CD	pos2=LS	11	nmod	_	U-MONEY
13	San	san	NNP	_	17	compound	_	B-ORG
14	Antonio	antonio	NNP	_	17	compound	_	I-ORG
15	Spurs	spur	NNPS	pos2=NNP	17	compound	_	I-ORG
16	RC	rc	NNP	pos2=GW	17	compound	_	I-ORG
17	HOF	hof	NNP	pos2=NN	18	dep	_	L-ORG
18	https://t.co/n44sfTNRNS	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NNP	20	nmod	_	O
19	#TimDuncan	#timduncan	ADD	pos2=-RRB-	0	root	_	U-ORG
20	#NBA	#nba	NN	pos2=ADD	19	pobj	_	O

