1	@joerogan	@joerogan	UH	pos2=NN	2	discourse	_	O
2	Is	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
3	there	there	EX	_	2	expl	_	O
4	anything	anything	NN	_	2	attr	_	O
5	good	good	JJ	_	4	nmod	_	O
6	about	about	IN	_	5	prep	_	O
7	the	the	DT	_	8	det	_	O
8	north	north	NN	_	6	pobj	_	O
9	?	?	.	_	2	punct	_	O

1	G	g	NN	pos2=NNP	6	nsubj	_	O
2	of	of	IN	_	1	prep	_	O
3	Thrones	throne	NNS	pos2=NNP	2	pobj	_	O
4	=	=	SYM	pos2=IN	6	punct	_	O
5	White	white	NNP	pos2=JJ	6	compound	_	O
6	Walkers	walker	NNPS	pos2=NNS	0	root	_	O
7	,	,	,	_	6	punct	_	O
8	N	n	NNP	pos2=VBZ	13	compound	_	B-GPE
9	Korea	korea	NNP	pos2=NN	13	nsubj	_	L-GPE
10	=	=	SYM	pos2=-LRB-	13	punct	_	O
11	Kim	kim	NNP	_	13	compound	_	B-PERSON
12	Jong	jong	NNP	_	13	compound	_	I-PERSON
13	Un	un	NNP	_	6	npadvmod	_	L-PERSON
14	,	,	,	_	6	punct	_	O
15	N	n	NNP	_	16	compound	_	B-ORG
16	Dakota	dakota	NNP	_	13	npadvmod	_	I-ORG
17	=	=	SYM	pos2=HYPH	18	punct	_	I-ORG
18	NoDAPL	nodapl	NNP	pos2=XX	16	conj	_	L-ORG
19	,	,	,	_	18	punct	_	O
20	N	n	NNP	pos2=JJ	21	compound	_	B-GPE
21	Carolina	carolina	NNP	_	24	nsubj	_	L-GPE
22	=	=	SYM	pos2=:	24	punct	_	O
23	Shitty	shitty	JJ	pos2=NNP	24	nmod	_	O
24	Gov	gov	NNP	pos2=NN	6	npadvmod	_	U-PRODUCT

