1	Japan	japan	NNP	_	2	nsubj	_	U-GPE
2	prepares	prepare	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
3	for	for	IN	_	2	prep	_	O
4	NUCLEAR	nuclear	JJ	pos2=NNP	5	nmod	_	O
5	war	war	NN	_	3	pobj	_	O
6	with	with	IN	_	5	prep	_	O
7	North	north	NNP	_	8	compound	_	B-GPE
8	Korea	korea	NNP	_	11	poss	_	I-GPE
9	's	's	POS	_	8	case	_	L-GPE
10	Genocidal	genocidal	JJ	pos2=NNP	11	nmod	_	O
11	Dictator	dictator	NNP	pos2=NN	6	pobj	_	O
12	,	,	,	_	2	punct	_	O
13	"	"	``	_	2	punct	_	O
14	Fat	fat	NNP	pos2=JJ	15	compound	_	O
15	Bastard	bastard	NNP	pos2=NN	21	dep	_	O
16	"	"	''	_	21	punct	_	O
17	Kim	kim	NNP	_	20	compound	_	B-PERSON
18	Jong	jong	NNP	_	20	compound	_	I-PERSON
19	-	-	HYPH	pos2=GW	20	punct	_	I-PERSON
20	Un	un	NNP	_	21	dep	_	L-PERSON
21	https://t.co/Ap3jmI1ZRc	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	2	dep	_	O

