1	Barron	barron	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Trump	trump	NNP	_	13	vocative	_	L-PERSON
3	,	,	,	_	2	punct	_	O
4	Donald	donald	NNP	_	2	conj	_	B-ORG
5	&	&	CC	_	4	cc	_	I-ORG
6	Melania	melania	NNP	_	4	conj	_	I-ORG
7	’s	's	POS	_	6	case	_	I-ORG
8	Son	son	NNP	pos2=NN	4	appos	_	L-ORG
9	:	:	:	_	4	punct	_	O
10	The	the	DT	_	11	det	_	O
11	Pictures	pictures	NNP	pos2=NNS	4	appos	_	O
12	You	you	PRP	pos2=NNP	13	nsubj	_	O
13	Need	need	VBP	_	0	root	_	O
14	to	to	TO	_	15	aux	_	O
15	See	see	VB	_	13	xcomp	_	O
16	https://t.co/X07aRx9RGq	#hlink#	ADD	_	17	nmod	_	O
17	https://t.co/Fa6NnnRceA	#hlink#	ADD	_	15	dobj	_	O

