1	Cop	cop	NN	pos2=NNP	2	compound	_	O
2	Killings	killing	NNS	pos2=NNPS	0	root	_	O
3	+	+	SYM	pos2=:	2	punct	_	O
4	Dustin	dustin	NNP	_	5	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	VanLiew	vanliew	NNP	_	2	appos	_	L-PERSON
6	,	,	,	_	5	punct	_	O
7	the	the	DT	_	8	det	_	O
8	diff	diff	NN	pos2=NNP	5	appos	_	O
9	Obama	obama	NNP	_	8	appos	_	B-ORG
10	&	&	CC	_	9	cc	_	I-ORG
11	Trump	trump	NNP	pos2=NN	9	conj	_	L-ORG
12	on	on	IN	_	8	prep	_	O
13	energy	energy	NN	_	14	compound	_	O
14	ind	ind	NN	pos2=FW	12	pobj	_	O
15	+	+	SYM	_	14	punct	_	O
16	Norman	norman	NNP	_	17	compound	_	B-PERSON
17	Anderson	anderson	NNP	_	18	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
18	is	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
19	on	on	IN	_	18	prep	_	O
20	fire	fire	NN	_	19	pobj	_	O
21	about	about	IN	_	18	prep	_	O
22	Trump	trump	NNP	pos2=NN	23	compound	_	B-PERSON
23	Admin	admin	NNP	pos2=NN	21	pobj	_	L-PERSON
24	!	!	.	_	18	punct	_	O

1	https://t.co/nBxUqDbD3C	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	U-ORG

