1	Report	report	NN	pos2=VB	6	dep	_	O
2	:	:	:	_	6	punct	_	O
3	Trump	trump	NNP	pos2=NN	5	compound	_	B-ORG
4	Transition	transition	NNP	pos2=NN	5	compound	_	I-ORG
5	Team	team	NNP	_	6	nsubj	_	L-ORG
6	Wants	want	VBZ	pos2=NNP	0	root	_	O
7	Mitt	mitt	NNP	_	8	compound	_	B-PERSON
8	Romney	romney	NNP	_	10	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
9	to	to	TO	pos2=IN	10	aux	_	O
10	Apologize	apologize	VB	pos2=NNP	6	ccomp	_	O
11	Publicly	publicly	RB	pos2=NNP	10	advmod	_	O
12	-	-	:	pos2=,	10	punct	_	O
13	The	the	DT	_	15	det	_	B-ORG
14	Epoch	epoch	NNP	_	15	compound	_	I-ORG
15	Times	times	NNP	pos2=GW	17	nmod	_	L-ORG
16	https://t.co/fmTLMdBnVs	#hlink#	ADD	_	17	dep	_	O
17	#Romney	#romney	NNP	pos2=-RRB-	10	dep	_	O

