1	Interesting	interesting	JJ	_	2	nmod	_	O
2	juxtaposition	juxtaposition	NN	_	0	root	_	O
3	of	of	IN	_	2	prep	_	O
4	story	story	NN	_	3	pobj	_	O
5	&	&	CC	_	4	cc	_	O
6	image	image	NN	_	4	conj	_	O
7	as	as	IN	_	14	mark	_	O
8	Kim	kim	NNP	_	11	compound	_	B-PERSON
9	Jong	jong	NNP	_	11	compound	_	I-PERSON
10	-	-	HYPH	_	11	punct	_	I-PERSON
11	un	un	NNP	_	14	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
12	has	have	VBZ	_	14	aux	_	O
13	just	just	RB	_	14	advmod	_	O
14	demanded	demand	VBN	_	2	advcl	_	O
15	more	more	RBR	pos2=JJR	16	advmod	_	O
16	involuntary	involuntary	JJ	_	18	nmod	_	O
17	volunteer	volunteer	NN	_	18	compound	_	O
18	work	work	NN	_	14	dobj	_	O
19	from	from	IN	_	18	prep	_	O
20	Women	women	NNP	pos2=NNS	22	poss	_	B-ORG
21	's	's	POS	_	20	case	_	I-ORG
22	Union	union	NNP	_	19	pobj	_	L-ORG
23	vs.	vs.	CC	pos2=IN	18	cc	_	O
24	sanctions	sanction	NNS	_	18	conj	_	O

