1	Bob	bob	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Dylan	dylan	NNP	_	18	dep	_	L-PERSON
3	,	,	,	_	2	punct	_	O
4	Seasick	seasick	NNP	_	5	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	Steve	steve	NNP	_	2	conj	_	L-PERSON
6	and	and	CC	_	5	cc	_	O
7	rock	rock	NN	pos2=NNP	10	poss	_	O
8	’s	's	POS	pos2=VBZ	7	case	_	O
9	great	great	JJ	_	10	nmod	_	O
10	hits	hit	NNS	_	5	conj	_	O
11	and	and	CC	_	10	cc	_	O
12	myths	myth	NNS	_	10	conj	_	O
13	–	-	:	pos2=,	18	punct	_	O
14	The	the	DT	_	17	det	_	B-ORG
15	Sydney	sydney	NNP	_	17	compound	_	I-ORG
16	Morning	morning	NNP	_	17	compound	_	I-ORG
17	Herald	herald	NNP	_	18	nmod	_	L-ORG
18	https://t.co/aPIpQBcvut	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	O

