1	https://t.co/qGSEXQkhk5	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	14	dep	_	O
2	2004	0	CD	pos2=LS	14	compound	_	U-DATE
3	Nike	nike	NNP	_	14	compound	_	B-ORG
4	Total	total	NNP	pos2=JJ	7	compound	_	I-ORG
5	Air	air	NNP	pos2=NN	6	compound	_	L-ORG
6	Foamposite	foamposite	NNP	_	10	compound	_	O
7	Max	max	NNP	_	10	compound	_	B-PERSON
8	Tim	tim	NNP	_	10	compound	_	I-PERSON
9	Duncan	duncan	NNP	_	10	compound	_	I-PERSON
10	White	white	NNP	_	14	dep	_	L-PERSON
11	/	/	SYM	pos2=HYPH	12	punct	_	O
12	black	black	JJ	pos2=NN	13	nmod	_	O
13	Size	size	NN	_	10	appos	_	O
14	9.5	0	CD	_	0	root	_	U-CARDINAL

