1	O.K.	o.k.	NNP	pos2=NFP	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Trump	trump	NNP	pos2=NN	4	vocative	_	L-PERSON
3	you	you	PRP	_	4	nsubj	_	O
4	won	win	VBD	_	10	ccomp	_	O
5	the	the	DT	_	6	det	_	O
6	election	election	NN	_	4	dobj	_	O
7	;	;	:	pos2=,	10	punct	_	O
8	do	do	VB	pos2=VBP	10	aux	_	O
9	n't	not	RB	_	10	neg	_	O
10	fuck	fuck	VB	_	0	root	_	O
11	with	with	IN	_	10	prep	_	O
12	Medicare	medicare	NNP	_	11	pobj	_	U-ORG
13	or	or	CC	_	12	cc	_	O
14	S.S.	s.s.	NNP	_	16	compound	_	B-ORG
15	Fuck	fuck	NNP	_	16	compound	_	I-ORG
16	Ryans	ryans	NNPS	_	18	poss	_	I-ORG
17	'	'	POS	_	16	case	_	L-ORG
18	proposal	proposal	NN	_	12	conj	_	O
19	to	to	IN	pos2=TO	20	aux	_	O
20	gut	gut	VB	pos2=NN	18	acl	_	O
21	Medicare	medicare	NNP	pos2=NN	20	dobj	_	B-ORG
22	&	&	CC	_	21	cc	_	I-ORG
23	Medicaid	medicaid	NNP	pos2=NN	21	conj	_	L-ORG
24	;	;	:	pos2=,	25	punct	_	O
25	Be	be	VB	_	10	dep	_	O
26	a	a	DT	_	27	det	_	O
27	FDR	fdr	NN	pos2=NNP	25	attr	_	O
28	!	!	.	_	10	punct	_	O

1	\	\	SYM	pos2=-RRB-	0	root	_	O

