1	@realDonaldTrump	@realdonaldtrump	NNP	pos2=XX	2	compound	_	B-GPE
2	People	people	NNPS	pos2=NNP	4	poss	_	I-GPE
3	's	's	POS	_	2	case	_	I-GPE
4	Republic	republic	NNP	_	8	nsubj	_	I-GPE
5	of	of	IN	_	4	prep	_	I-GPE
6	China	china	NNP	_	5	pobj	_	L-GPE
7	,	,	,	_	8	punct	_	O
8	is	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
9	a	a	DT	_	10	det	_	O
10	state	state	NN	_	8	attr	_	O
11	governed	govern	VBN	_	10	acl	_	O
12	by	by	IN	_	11	agent	_	O
13	the	the	DT	_	15	det	_	B-ORG
14	Communist	communist	NNP	_	15	compound	_	I-ORG
15	Party	party	NNP	_	12	pobj	_	I-ORG
16	of	of	IN	_	15	prep	_	I-ORG
17	China	china	NNP	_	16	pobj	_	L-ORG
18	.	.	.	_	8	punct	_	O

1	We	we	PRP	_	2	nsubj	_	O
2	trade	trade	VBP	pos2=VB	0	root	_	O
3	with	with	IN	_	2	prep	_	O
4	them	them	PRP	_	3	pobj	_	O
5	but	but	CC	_	2	cc	_	O
6	Embargo	embargo	NNP	_	7	compound	_	O
7	Cuba	cuba	NNP	_	4	conj	_	U-GPE
8	???	??	.	_	2	punct	_	O

