1	TIL	til	NNP	pos2=FW	2	compound	_	U-ORG
2	veganism	veganism	NN	_	3	nsubj	_	O
3	is	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
4	a	a	DT	_	5	det	_	O
5	type	type	NN	_	3	attr	_	O
6	of	of	IN	_	5	prep	_	O
7	vegetarianism	vegetarianism	NN	_	6	pobj	_	O
8	along	along	IN	pos2=RB	5	prep	_	O
9	with	with	IN	_	8	prep	_	O
10	Lacto	lacto	NNP	_	11	compound	_	B-PERSON
11	Vegetarian	vegetarian	NNP	pos2=JJ	9	pobj	_	L-PERSON
12	,	,	,	_	11	punct	_	O
13	Ovo	ovo	NNP	_	16	compound	_	B-ORG
14	-	-	HYPH	pos2=:	16	punct	_	I-ORG
15	Lacto	lacto	NNP	_	16	compound	_	I-ORG
16	Vegetarian	vegetarian	NNP	pos2=JJ	11	conj	_	L-ORG
17	,	,	,	_	16	punct	_	O
18	Ovo	ovo	NNP	_	19	compound	_	B-PERSON
19	Vegetarian	vegetarian	NNP	pos2=JJ	16	conj	_	L-PERSON
20	and	and	CC	_	19	cc	_	O
21	vegans	vegan	NNS	_	19	conj	_	O
22	do	do	VBP	_	24	aux	_	O
23	not	not	RB	_	24	neg	_	O
24	consume	consume	VB	_	27	ccomp	_	O
25	not	not	RB	_	26	neg	_	O
26	onl	onl	NN	pos2=JJ	24	dobj	_	O
27	…	…	.	pos2=''	3	punct	_	O

