1	Northern	northern	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-ORG
2	League	league	NNP	_	5	poss	_	I-ORG
3	’s	's	POS	_	2	case	_	L-ORG
4	Matteo	matteo	NNP	_	5	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	Salvini	salvini	NNP	_	10	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
6	and	and	CC	_	5	cc	_	O
7	Marine	marine	NNP	pos2=JJ	9	compound	_	B-ORG
8	Le	le	NNP	_	9	compound	_	I-ORG
9	Pen	pen	NNP	_	5	conj	_	L-ORG
10	are	be	VBP	_	12	aux	_	O
11	both	both	DT	pos2=RB	12	dep	_	O
12	celebrating	celebrate	VBG	_	0	root	_	O
13	the	the	DT	pos2=PRP	15	det	_	O
14	No	no	DT	pos2=NNP	15	det	_	O
15	vote	vote	NN	_	12	dobj	_	O
16	in	in	IN	_	12	prep	_	O
17	the	the	DT	_	20	det	_	O
18	Italian	italian	JJ	_	20	nmod	_	U-NORP
19	constitutional	constitutional	JJ	_	20	nmod	_	O
20	referendum	referendum	NN	_	16	pobj	_	O
21	.	.	.	_	12	punct	_	O

1	Hmm.	hmm.	NN	pos2=FW	0	root	_	O

