1	London	london	NNP	_	6	nmod	_	O
2	,	,	,	_	1	punct	_	O
3	United	united	NNP	_	4	compound	_	O
4	Kingdom	kingdom	NNP	_	0	root	_	O
5	|	|	SYM	pos2=HYPH	4	cc	_	O
6	AFP	afp	NNP	pos2=NN	11	dep	_	B-ORG
7	|	|	SYM	pos2=:	12	punct	_	I-ORG
8	Manchester	manchester	NNP	_	9	compound	_	I-ORG
9	United	united	NNP	_	10	compound	_	L-ORG
10	manager	manager	NN	_	12	compound	_	O
11	Jose	jose	NNP	_	12	compound	_	B-PERSON
12	Mourinho	mourinho	NNP	_	0	root	_	L-PERSON
13	and	and	CC	_	12	cc	_	O
14	Real	real	NNP	pos2=JJ	15	compound	_	B-ORG
15	Madrid	madrid	NNP	_	16	compound	_	L-ORG
16	superstar	superstar	NN	pos2=NNP	17	compound	_	O
17	Cristiano	cristiano	NNP	_	12	conj	_	U-PERSON
18	...	..	.	pos2=,	17	punct	_	O

1	https://t.co/fLqc9v6oCv	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	U-ORG

