1	Cristiano	cristiano	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Ronaldo	ronaldo	NNP	_	7	dep	_	L-PERSON
3	,	,	,	_	2	punct	_	O
4	Georgina	georgina	NNP	_	7	compound	_	B-ORG
5	Rodriguez	rodriguez	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
6	Engagement	engagement	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
7	News	news	NNP	pos2=NN	15	nsubj	_	L-ORG
8	and	and	CC	_	7	cc	_	O
9	Updates	update	NNS	pos2=NNPS	7	conj	_	O
10	:	:	:	_	9	punct	_	O
11	Real	real	NNP	pos2=JJ	13	compound	_	B-ORG
12	Madrid	madrid	NNP	_	13	compound	_	I-ORG
13	Star	star	NNP	_	15	nsubj	_	L-ORG
14	Has	have	VBZ	pos2=NNP	15	aux	_	O
15	Introduced	introduce	VBN	_	0	root	_	O
16	New	new	NNP	pos2=JJ	15	dobj	_	O
17	...	..	.	pos2=,	15	punct	_	O

1	-…	-…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	2	punct	_	O
2	https://t.co/5MQL8bANzV	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	0	root	_	O

