1	Why	why	WRB	_	4	advmod	_	O
2	did	do	VBD	_	4	aux	_	O
3	n't	not	RB	_	4	neg	_	O
4	@jaketapper	@jaketapper	VB	pos2=PRP$	0	root	_	O
5	report	report	VB	pos2=NN	4	xcomp	_	O
6	that	that	IN	pos2=DT	14	mark	_	O
7	mass	mass	NN	pos2=JJ	8	compound	_	O
8	shooter	shooter	NN	_	12	compound	_	O
9	Floyd	floyd	NNP	_	12	compound	_	B-PERSON
10	Lee	lee	NNP	_	12	compound	_	I-PERSON
11	Corkins	corkins	NNP	_	12	compound	_	I-PERSON
12	II	ii	NNP	pos2=CD	14	nsubjpass	_	L-PERSON
13	was	be	VBD	_	14	auxpass	_	O
14	inspired	inspire	VBN	_	5	ccomp	_	O
15	by	by	IN	_	14	agent	_	O
16	Southern	southern	NNP	_	19	compound	_	B-ORG
17	Poverty	poverty	NNP	_	19	compound	_	I-ORG
18	Law	law	NNP	_	19	compound	_	I-ORG
19	Center	center	NNP	_	15	pobj	_	L-ORG
20	?	?	.	_	4	punct	_	O

1	https://t.co/dzAPgiqcql	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	U-ORG

