1	Jesuit	jesuit	NNP	pos2=JJ	2	compound	_	U-NORP
2	MAN	man	NN	pos2=NNP	7	nsubj	_	O
3	of	of	IN	_	2	prep	_	O
4	SIN	sin	NNP	pos2=NN	5	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	Pope	pope	NNP	_	3	pobj	_	L-PERSON
6	https://t.co/kYcVYMf0wC	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NNP	7	nsubj	_	O
7	took	take	VBD	_	0	root	_	O
8	this	this	DT	_	11	det	_	O
9	complete	complete	JJ	_	11	nmod	_	O
10	Jesuit	jesuit	NNP	_	11	compound	_	B-ORG
11	Oath	oath	NNP	pos2=NN	7	dobj	_	I-ORG
12	of	of	IN	_	11	prep	_	I-ORG
13	Extreme	extreme	NNP	pos2=JJ	14	compound	_	I-ORG
14	Induction	induction	NNP	pos2=NN	12	pobj	_	L-ORG
15	.	.	.	_	7	punct	_	O

1	WHO	who	WP	_	2	attr	_	O
2	IS	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
3	THE	the	DT	_	5	det	_	O
4	ONE	#crd#	CD	pos2=NNP	5	nmod	_	U-CARDINAL
5	T	t	NN	pos2=GW	2	nsubj	_	O
6	…	…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	7	punct	_	O
7	https://t.co/6KkcS0PD4A	#hlink#	ADD	_	5	appos	_	U-ORG

