1	Book	book	NNP	pos2=VB	0	root	_	U-ORG
2	now	now	RB	_	3	advmod	_	O
3	for	for	IN	_	1	prep	_	O
4	‘	'	``	pos2=''	3	punct	_	O
5	The	the	DT	_	6	det	_	B-ORG
6	Power	power	NN	pos2=NNP	3	pobj	_	I-ORG
7	of	of	IN	_	6	prep	_	I-ORG
8	Film	film	NN	pos2=NNP	7	pobj	_	I-ORG
9	:	:	:	_	10	punct	_	I-ORG
10	Ali	ali	NNP	_	8	appos	_	I-ORG
11	in	in	IN	_	10	prep	_	I-ORG
12	the	the	DT	_	13	det	_	I-ORG
13	Movies	movies	NNP	pos2=NNPS	11	pobj	_	I-ORG
14	&	&	CC	_	13	cc	_	I-ORG
15	Popular	popular	NNP	pos2=JJ	16	compound	_	I-ORG
16	Media	media	NNP	pos2=NNS	13	conj	_	L-ORG
17	with	with	IN	_	10	prep	_	O
18	Bro	bro	NNP	_	19	compound	_	B-PERSON
19	Hakim	hakim	NNP	_	17	pobj	_	L-PERSON
20	on	on	IN	_	10	prep	_	O
21	Wed	wed	NNP	pos2=VBD	20	pobj	_	O
22	7	0	CD	_	21	nmod	_	O
23	Dec	dec	NNP	_	25	compound	_	O
24	@HackneyAttic	@hackneyattic	NN	pos2=JJ	25	compound	_	O
25	Info	info	NN	pos2=NNP	10	appos	_	O
26	:	:	:	_	10	punct	_	O
27	…	…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	28	punct	_	O
28	https://t.co/Pule0yjytx	#hlink#	ADD	_	10	appos	_	O

