1	A	a	DT	_	5	det	_	O
2	top	top	JJ	pos2=NN	5	nmod	_	O
3	Google	google	NNP	_	5	compound	_	U-ORG
4	search	search	NN	_	5	compound	_	O
5	question	question	NN	_	0	root	_	O
6	for	for	IN	_	5	prep	_	O
7	the	the	DT	_	9	det	_	B-ORG
8	Catholic	catholic	NNP	_	9	compound	_	I-ORG
9	Church	church	NNP	_	6	pobj	_	L-ORG
10	?	?	.	_	5	punct	_	O

1	"	"	``	_	2	punct	_	O
2	Is	be	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
3	the	the	DT	_	6	det	_	B-PERSON
4	Catholic	catholic	NNP	pos2=JJ	6	compound	_	I-PERSON
5	Church	church	NNP	_	6	compound	_	I-PERSON
6	Satanic	satanic	NNP	pos2=JJ	2	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
7	?	?	.	pos2=,	2	punct	_	O
8	"	"	''	_	2	punct	_	O

1	.	.	.	_	0	punct	_	O

1	For	for	IN	_	9	prep	_	O
2	Pope	pope	NNP	_	1	pobj	_	O
3	Francis	francis	NNP	_	9	dep	_	O
4	-	-	HYPH	pos2=,	9	punct	_	O
5	"	"	``	pos2=''	6	punct	_	O
6	Is	be	VBZ	_	9	nmod	_	O
7	Pop	pop	GW	pos2=NN	9	nmod	_	O
8	…	…	NFP	pos2=GW	9	nmod	_	O
9	https://t.co/wq802Mig2H	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	0	root	_	O

