1	Muhammad	muhammad	NNP	_	3	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Ali	ali	NNP	_	3	compound	_	I-PERSON
3	Heated	heated	NNP	pos2=VBD	4	compound	_	L-PERSON
4	Argument	argument	NN	pos2=NNP	14	nsubj	_	O
5	with	with	IN	_	4	prep	_	O
6	Black	black	NNP	pos2=JJ	7	compound	_	B-ORG
7	Singer	singer	NNP	pos2=NN	5	pobj	_	I-ORG
8	&	&	CC	_	7	cc	_	I-ORG
9	White	white	NNP	pos2=JJ	10	compound	_	L-ORG
10	Congressman	congressman	NNP	pos2=NN	7	conj	_	O
11	https://t.co/pgBTMXIikb	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NNP	7	appos	_	O
12	via	via	IN	_	4	prep	_	O
13	@YouTube	@youtube	NNP	pos2=ADD	12	pobj	_	O
14	@RealDonaldTrump	@realdonaldtrump	ADD	pos2=NN	0	root	_	O

