1	L	l	JJ	pos2=NN	2	nmod	_	O
2	#ZacEfron	#zacefron	ADD	pos2=NN	10	dep	_	O
3	#Fashion	#fashion	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	O
4	ZAC	zac	NNP	_	10	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	EFRON	efron	NNP	_	10	compound	_	L-PERSON
6	CHARLIE	charlie	NNP	_	10	compound	_	B-PERSON
7	ST	st	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	L-PERSON
8	CLOUD	cloud	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	B-GPE
9	BLU	blu	NNP	pos2=NN	10	compound	_	I-GPE
10	RAY	ray	NNP	pos2=NN	0	root	_	L-GPE
11	IN	in	IN	pos2=NNP	10	prep	_	O
12	ORIGINAL	original	JJ	_	13	nmod	_	O
13	CASE	case	NN	_	11	pobj	_	O
14	,	,	,	_	10	punct	_	O
15	MINT	mint	NN	pos2=NNP	16	compound	_	O
16	CONDITION	condition	NN	_	10	dep	_	O
17	!!	!!	.	_	10	punct	_	O

1	#Actor	#actor	NNP	pos2=GW	3	nmod	_	B-PERSON
2	#BestSeller	#bestseller	GW	pos2=ADD	3	nmod	_	L-PERSON
3	https://t.co/IGypLDlbus	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	O

