1	Cristiano	cristiano	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Ronaldo	ronaldo	NNP	_	3	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
3	shows	show	VBZ	_	0	root	_	O
4	off	off	RP	pos2=IN	3	prt	_	O
5	his	his	PRP$	_	7	poss	_	O
6	ridiculous	ridiculous	JJ	_	7	nmod	_	O
7	legs	leg	NNS	_	3	dobj	_	O
8	as	as	IN	_	3	prep	_	O
9	Real	real	NNP	pos2=JJ	10	compound	_	B-ORG
10	Madrid	madrid	NNP	_	8	pobj	_	L-ORG
11	forward	forward	RB	pos2=NNP	12	advmod	_	O
12	continues	continue	VBZ	_	3	conj	_	O
13	countdown	countdown	NN	pos2=VBG	12	dobj	_	O
14	to	to	IN	_	12	prep	_	O
15	El	el	NNP	_	18	compound	_	B-ORG
16	Clasico	clasico	NNP	_	18	compound	_	I-ORG
17	-	-	HYPH	pos2=SYM	18	punct	_	I-ORG
18	Mirror	mirror	NNP	_	14	pobj	_	L-ORG
19	.	.	.	_	3	punct	_	O

1	…	…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	2	punct	_	O
2	https://t.co/a8goLEBvdb	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	0	root	_	O

