1	Jim	jim	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Willie	willie	NNP	_	6	vocative	_	L-PERSON
3	2017	0	CD	_	4	nmod	_	O
4	Elites	elite	NNS	pos2=NNPS	0	root	_	O
5	In	in	IN	_	4	prep	_	O
6	Fear	fear	NN	pos2=NNP	5	pobj	_	O
7	Of	of	IN	_	6	prep	_	O
8	White	white	NNP	_	10	compound	_	B-ORG
9	Dragon	dragon	NNP	_	10	compound	_	I-ORG
10	Society	society	NNP	_	7	pobj	_	I-ORG
11	&	&	CC	_	10	cc	_	I-ORG
12	Gold	gold	NNP	pos2=NN	13	compound	_	I-ORG
13	Standard	standard	NNP	pos2=JJ	10	conj	_	L-ORG
14	https://t.co/3Kwzqer7WW	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NNP	16	dep	_	O
15	via	via	IN	_	4	prep	_	O
16	@YouTube	@youtube	NNP	pos2=NN	15	pobj	_	O

