1	Election	election	NN	pos2=NNP	0	root	_	O
2	of	of	IN	_	1	prep	_	O
3	Dr	dr	NNP	_	5	compound	_	O
4	Hélène	hélène	NNP	_	5	compound	_	B-PERSON
5	RENOUX	renoux	NNP	pos2=NN	2	pobj	_	L-PERSON
6	as	as	IN	_	1	prep	_	O
7	Chairman	chairman	NNP	_	6	pobj	_	O
8	of	of	IN	_	7	prep	_	O
9	the	the	DT	_	11	det	_	B-ORG
10	European	european	NNP	pos2=JJ	11	compound	_	I-ORG
11	Committee	committee	NNP	_	8	pobj	_	I-ORG
12	of	of	IN	_	11	prep	_	I-ORG
13	Homeopathy	homeopathy	NNP	pos2=NN	12	pobj	_	L-ORG
14	,	,	,	_	17	punct	_	O
15	on	on	IN	_	11	prep	_	O
16	20	0	CD	_	17	nmod	_	B-DATE
17	Nov	nov	NNP	_	15	pobj	_	I-DATE
18	2016	0	CD	_	17	npadvmod	_	L-DATE
19	.	.	.	_	1	punct	_	O

1	The	the	DT	_	5	det	_	O
2	entire	entire	JJ	_	6	nmod	_	O
3	FMRC	fmrc	NNP	pos2=NN	6	nmod	_	U-ORG
4	t	t	GW	pos2=NN	6	nmod	_	O
5	…	…	GW	pos2=NFP	6	nmod	_	O
6	https://t.co/0jqMmUiyov	#hlink#	ADD	pos2=NN	0	root	_	U-ORG

