1	New	new	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-ORG
2	York	york	NNP	_	3	compound	_	I-ORG
3	State	state	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
4	Tweaks	tweaks	NNP	pos2=VBZ	7	compound	_	I-ORG
5	Medical	medical	NNP	pos2=JJ	7	compound	_	I-ORG
6	Marijuana	marijuana	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
7	Law	law	NNP	_	19	dep	_	L-ORG
8	,	,	,	_	7	punct	_	O
9	But	but	CC	_	7	cc	_	O
10	no	no	DT	_	11	det	_	O
11	Signs	sign	NNS	pos2=NNPS	7	conj	_	O
12	of	of	IN	_	11	prep	_	O
13	Legalization	legalization	NNP	pos2=NN	12	pobj	_	O
14	Yet	yet	CC	pos2=NNP	7	cc	_	O
15	|	|	SYM	pos2=,	19	punct	_	O
16	NBC	nbc	NNP	_	18	compound	_	U-ORG
17	New	new	NNP	_	18	compound	_	B-GPE
18	York	york	NNP	pos2=GW	19	dep	_	L-GPE
19	https://t.co/btWNagjEZC	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	O

