1	The	the	DT	_	3	det	_	O
2	“	"	``	_	3	punct	_	O
3	Concern	concern	NN	pos2=NNP	22	dep	_	O
4	”	"	''	_	3	punct	_	O
5	about	about	IN	_	3	prep	_	O
6	Pope	pope	NNP	_	7	compound	_	O
7	Francis	francis	NNP	_	5	pobj	_	U-PERSON
8	by	by	IN	_	3	prep	_	O
9	Fr.	fr.	NNP	_	12	compound	_	O
10	James	james	NNP	_	12	compound	_	B-PERSON
11	V.	v.	NNP	_	12	compound	_	I-PERSON
12	Schall	schall	NNP	_	8	pobj	_	L-PERSON
13	,	,	,	_	12	punct	_	O
14	S.J.	s.j.	NNP	_	12	npadvmod	_	U-GPE
15	,	,	,	_	12	punct	_	O
16	of	of	IN	_	12	prep	_	O
17	Crisis	crisis	NNP	_	18	compound	_	B-ORG
18	Magazine	magazine	NNP	pos2=NN	16	pobj	_	I-ORG
19	https://t.co/uMRi5Wv1nl	#hlink#	ADD	_	22	dep	_	I-ORG
20	#God	#god	NNP	pos2=-RRB-	22	dep	_	L-ORG
21	…	…	NFP	pos2=-LRB-	22	punct	_	O
22	https://t.co/mUH6d0XLJI	#hlink#	ADD	_	0	root	_	U-ORG

