1	The	the	DT	_	3	det	_	O
2	curious	curious	JJ	_	3	nmod	_	O
3	case	case	NN	_	0	root	_	O
4	of	of	IN	_	3	prep	_	O
5	charles	charles	NNP	pos2=FW	6	compound	_	B-PERSON
6	darwin	darwin	NNP	pos2=NN	4	pobj	_	L-PERSON
7	and	and	CC	_	6	cc	_	O
8	homeopathy	homeopathy	NN	_	6	conj	_	O
9	.	.	.	_	3	punct	_	O

1	Ullman	ullman	NNP	_	7	compound	_	B-ORG
2	D.	d.	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
3	Evid	evid	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
4	Based	based	NNP	pos2=VBN	7	compound	_	I-ORG
5	Complement	complement	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
6	Alternat	alternat	NNP	_	7	compound	_	I-ORG
7	Med	med	NNP	_	11	nsubj	_	L-ORG
8	;	;	,	pos2=:	7	punct	_	O
9	2010	0	CD	_	10	nmod	_	U-DATE
10	Mar	mar	NNP	_	14	npadvmod	_	O
11	;	;	,	pos2=:	0	root	_	O
12	7	0	CD	_	13	nmod	_	B-DATE
13	(1)	(0)	CD	pos2=SYM	14	nsubj	_	I-DATE
14	:33-9	0	CD	_	7	appos	_	L-DATE
15	.	.	.	_	7	punct	_	O

