1	Fidel	fidel	NNP	_	2	compound	_	B-PERSON
2	Castro	castro	NNP	_	11	nsubj	_	L-PERSON
3	a	a	DT	_	4	det	_	O
4	friend	friend	NN	_	2	appos	_	O
5	of	of	IN	_	4	prep	_	O
6	the	the	DT	_	10	det	_	B-ORG
7	Poor	poor	NNP	pos2=JJ	9	compound	_	I-ORG
8	Working	working	NNP	_	9	compound	_	I-ORG
9	Class	class	NNP	_	10	compound	_	I-ORG
10	People	people	NNPS	pos2=NNP	11	nsubj	_	L-ORG
11	leaves	leave	VBZ	_	22	ccomp	_	O
12	£	$	$	_	13	nmod	_	O
13	900,000,000	0	CD	_	11	dobj	_	U-MONEY
14	What	what	WDT	pos2=WP	16	det	_	O
15	a	a	DT	_	16	det	_	O
16	Shame	shame	NN	pos2=NNP	11	dobj	_	O
17	,	,	,	_	22	punct	_	O
18	how	how	WRB	_	22	advmod	_	O
19	will	will	MD	_	22	aux	_	O
20	his	his	PRP$	_	21	poss	_	O
21	family	family	NN	_	22	nsubj	_	O
22	Cope	cope	VB	pos2=NNP	0	root	_	O
23	?	?	.	_	22	punct	_	O

